Jiushuang, don't worry.
You're from the Mei Family.
That Sheng Lingyu won't dare touch you.
Actually, the Dragon-Seeking Lineage's
Zhang Family still has a descendant.
I strive to be Head of the Four Clans.
I'll surely help you find the Tidal Tomb.
Is everything you said true?
Jiushuang.
How could I ever bear to lie to you?
Once I become the Mei Family son-in-law,
I will find that descendant
and save the four families from disaster.
Jiushuang, don't worry.
Even if I'm imprisoned,
I'd risk my life to keep you safe.
He's really playing the devoted lover.
What are you doing?
Let me go!
Hey!
What are you doing?!
Where are you taking him?
Li Xiao!
Why are you taking him?
I'm exhausted.
Mouse!
Did you see that just now?
I saw it.
It looked like a person.
But maybe it wasn't.
I think I touched it.
A ghost!
Mouse!
Young Master!
What are you running around for?
How dare you run around here?
Do you have a death wish?
Qi Tianting!
Li Xiao, you're really something.
I want the item.
And I want her, too.
So, what do we do next?
Next?
Next, we get down to business, of course.
Qi Tianting!
Why are you here?
That bastard Qi Tiankun!
He locked me up here to die!
Zhang Tianyou!
Speaking of which...
This is all your fault!
Watch your mouth!
You two fight over the family fortune,
how does that concern our Young Master?
Still making sarcastic remarks?
I'll... I'll strangle you!
Come on, try it! Come on!
Okay, okay, okay.
Cramp, cramp, cramp...
I've got a cramp!
H-h-help me!
What's that sound?
What is this?
Who is it?
Second Young Master.
What's going on?
Family Head.
Who are you people?
How dare you trespass on the Qi Family!
I'm Li Xiao,
the chosen son-in-law of the Mei Family.
And if I wanted to,
I could be the Sheng Family son-in-law.
You...
What do you want?
Don't worry.
Your Qi Family only has men,
so I'm not interested.
Then...
Then why did you bring armed men here?
The deadline is near.
Even the Qi and Sheng Family Heads
couldn't escape disaster.
I'm obviously here to save you,
the last remaining heir of the Qi Family.
I have the Earth Vein Sutra
and the Celestial Seal now,
and the Talisman Book
is with your Qi Family.
That leaves only the tricky Wan Family.
The Wan Family?
If the Wan Family
sees I control the other three families,
they'd risk their entire clan's lives
than let me be Head of the Four Clans.
I know exactly what those people are like.
Li Xiao,
what do you need me to do?
All of you, step down for now.
I want you to take over the Sheng Family,
become their son-in-law,
and then imprison Mei Jiushuang.
Then, if the Wan and Mei families
want to find that tomb,
they will target you.
Once you're set up as the target,
I'll step forward,
pretending to help them deal with you.
That way, everyone will only trust me.
That's not fair to me.
Qi Tiankun,
only I can find that tomb
and save the entire clan.
Got it?
Then what should I do next?
Make a big scene.
Force Sheng Lingyu into marriage.
All right.
Young Master.
Should we help him out?
Sure.
Here.
Who needs your help?
Let's go.
You're just leaving like that?
That's so irresponsible.
Still acting tough?
Wait.
Fine.
Come on.
Qi Tianting, where exactly are we?
This place?
The secret room behind the Qi estate.
My father discovered this place years ago.
But he said
because of the feng shui here,
it is a Sinister Land.
We can't go deep for tomb raiding.
So he set up that Sealed Door outside.
What's inside?
It's a Sealed Door for a reason!
It's sealed, so I don't know!
But recently I've been locked in here,
and I keep hearing strange noises.
What is it?
Did you see a shadow pass by?
W-w-what shadow?
Did that shadow have a head?
Could it be that headless corpse?
A headless corpse? How could it stand up?
It's already a corpse!
Maybe my eyes played tricks on me.
Don't scare me!
Young Master, I'm easily scared as it is.
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
Why did you tap me?
Who tapped you?
A ghost!